<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="delay_explanation">In order to preserve battery power, some methods were used that will cause up to a 5 second delay in the status updates.</string>
<string name="gateway_page">The Gateway tab displays information about this device\'s connections to the gateways.</string>

<string name="gateway_statuses_debug"></string>

<!-- Text_One can have these statuses if not connected -->
<string name="gw_t1_pending">The distributor has the message, but cannot send it. This may be due to the lack of an available netlink.</string>
<string name="gw_t1_exception">AmmoCore needs restarted.</string>
<string name="gw_t1_connecting">Attempting to connect to the gateway.</string>
<string name="gw_t1_disconnected">The gateway is not connected.</string>
<string name="gw_t1_stale">The state of the Gateway connection is uncertain and AmmoCore is checking.</string>
<string name="gw_t1_linking">Attempting to find a valid netlink to use.</string>
<string name="gw_t1_linked">Connected to a netlink.</string>
<string name="gw_t1_waiting">AmmoCore needs restarted.</string>
<string name="gw_t1_shutdown">The connection has been shutdown and needs to be reestablished.</string>
<string name="gw_t1_interrupted">AmmoCore needs restarted.</string>
<string name="gw_t1_start">The message header is being read.</string>
<string name="gw_t1_started">The message is being read.</string>
<string name="gw_t1_transmitting">There is a connection to the Gateway and data can be transmitted.</string>
<!-- Text_One can have these if connected -->
<string name="gw_t1_sending">AmmoCore is currently sending a message to the Gateway.</string>
<string name="gw_t1_taking">AmmoCore is currently receiving a message from the Gateway.</string>
<!--This set also uses waiting -->


<!-- Text Two can have these only if connected,
		otherwise, it is invisible -->
<string name="gw_t2_checked">The message\'s checksum has been confirmed.</string>
<string name="gw_t2_deliver">The message has been delivered to the distributor.</string>
<string name="gw_t2_waiting">The message thread is waiting.</string>
<string name="gw_t2_start">The message header is being read.</string>
<string name="gw_t2_sized">The size of the message has been determined.</string>


<string name="netlink_page">The Netlinks tab displays information about the various data connections on this device.</string>

<string name="nsd_up">IP traffic should be available.</string>
<string name="nsd_down">IP traffic is not available. Attempt to connect the netlink.</string>
<string name="nsd_disabled">The netlink is disabled and cannot be used.</string>
<string name="nsd_disconnected">IP traffic is not available. Attempt to connect the netlink.</string>
<string name="nsd_idle">Ready to start data connection setup.</string>
<string name="nsd_scanning">Searching for an available access point.</string>
<string name="nsd_connecting">The device is attempting to connect with the netlink.</string>
<string name="nsd_auth">Link is established; performing authentication.</string>
<string name="nsd_obt_ip">The device is attempting to obtain an IP address from a DHCP server.</string>
<string name="nsd_failed">The connection attempt has failed. Attempt to reconnect.</string>
<string name="nsd_conn">IP traffic should be available.</string>
<string name="nsd_susp">IP traffic is suspended.</string>
<string name="nsd_u_avail">The Netlink is available for traffic.</string>
<string name="nsd_u_lost">The Netlink is not available for traffic.</string>
<string name="nsd_u_init">The Netlink is attempting to become available. Details of this depend on the Netlink type.</string>


<string name="prefs_gw_ip">The IP address of the Gateway.</string>
<string name="prefs_gw_port">The port to connect to the Gateway on.</string>
<string name="ntwk_conn_timeout">When attempting to connect, on a slow network, you may need a larger timeout. If you are having connection problems, try increasing this value.</string>
<string name="conn_idle_timeout">Heartbeat timeout. If a connection is idle for this time period, then it will disconnect and attempt to reconnect.</string>
<string name="user_id">The ID of the device\'s user.</string>
<string name="ammo_license">Copyright (C) 2010-2013 Institute for Software Integrated Systems (ISIS)
This software was developed by the Institute for Software Integrated
Systems (ISIS) at Vanderbilt University, Tennessee, USA for the 
Transformative Apps program under DARPA, Contract # HR011-10-C-0175.
The United States Government has unlimited rights to this software. 
The US government has the right to use, modify, reproduce, release, 
perform, display, or disclose computer software or computer software 
documentation in whole or in part, in any manner and for any 
purpose whatsoever, and to have or authorize others to do so.</string>
</resources>
